tboblogs.com 2018-08-22

# Privacy Policy | tboblogs

This privacy policy document is a detailed description of what personal information is collected and recorded by tboblogs.com and how we use it.

## Log Files

The log files that may be collected by tboblogs.com includes:

  * internet protocol (IP) addresses,
  * browser type,
  * Internet Service Provider (ISP),
  * date/time stamp,
  * referring/exit pages,
  * and possibly the number of clicks.

This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information.

IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

## Cookies

Theblogs.com does not use cookies.

## Children’s Information

We believe it is important to provide added protection for children online. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children to observe, participate in and/or monitor and guide their online activity. Tboblogs.com does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes that theblogs.com has in its database the personally-identifiable information of a child under the age of 13, please contact us immediately via online contact form and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there. This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

## Consent

By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.

## Update

This Privacy Policy was last updated on: Wednesday, October 11th, 2017.  
Should we update, amend or make any changes to our privacy policy, those changes will be posted here.
